Akash Yadav (Frontend Developer)

New Delhi, India | +91 8447610087 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/Akash-yadav0624/ | https://github.com/AKASH-YADAV0624 | akashyadav0624@gmail.com

ABOUT

Frontend Web Developer with professional development experience in creating robust web applications and e-commerce platforms. I bring a keen attention to detail and a strong set of technical skills to the table. Always excited to expand technical proficiencies.

SKILLS

- C++
- HTML ,CSS ,JAVASCRIPT
- REACTJS
- OOPS (Object oriented programming structure), DSA (Data Structure and algorithms)
- BOOTSTRAP,SQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Work as a Freelance Engineer

08/2023-10/2023

Techcurator

- Problem creation work
- Coding problem creation in C++
- Work using object oriented programming.

Web Developer 06/2024-Present

Helping Hut

- Making website using frontend technology html, css, javascript
- Work on SEO
- Translate design and wireframes into high quality and pixels perfect code.
- Creating official website of helping hut ngo.

EDUCATION

Maharshi Dayanand University, Rohtak

08/2019 - 06/2023

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science Engineering

GRM ,Sr , Sec Public School, Delhi

04/2017-05/2018

Senior Secondary, CBSE

PROJECTS

Super mart e-commerce website

- It is a functional Amazon-clone with all the features of an e-commerce website, maintained and deployed using Firebase for real-time database functionality.
- Technologies used React Js, Javascript, CSS, HTML, Firebase, No SQL

Cool games

- https://coolgaming.vercel.app/
- Our platform is designed to provide you with a seamless and exciting gaming adventure, combined with an optimized folder structure and codebase to ensure top-notch performance and maintainability.

Anime clothing website

- https://anime-clothing-website.vercel.app/
- Designed and implemented an intuitive and appealing user interface for seamless navigation.